[{"question": " hey! i got you a present!!", "answer": " oh my goodness! where did you hide it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i got it for your wedding and i ordered it weeks ago, and it finally got here!", "answer": " pheebs you didn&#146;t have to get us anything for our wedding you already sang&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " it&#146;s a ms. pac-man machine!!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t know where to put it so i just left it here for now.", "answer": " oh well, maybe we can put it in the guest bedroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh, okay.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i kinda like it here.", "answer": " do you really like it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " are you kidding?! i practically spent my entire childhood at the arcade! this is like&#151;oh my, this is like my second favorite game!", "answer": " oh really? what was your first?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well i-i really don&#146;t remember the name of it.", "answer": " well what did it do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " well, you just&#151;you put a quarter in and y&#146;know pull-pull some handles and win like a candy bar or something.", "answer": " a vending machine?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey! oh, i&#146;m so glad you guys are here. i&#146;ve been dying to tell someone what happened in the paleontology department today.", "answer": "  do you think he saw us or can we still sneak out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " professor neuman, the head of the department, so&#133;.", "answer": " they made you head of the department!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh! hey rach, listen umm&#133;", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " i got a big date coming up, do you know a good restaurant?", "answer": " uh, paul&#146;s caf\u008f. they got great food and it&#146;s really romantic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " ooh, great! thanks!", "answer": " yeah! oh, and then afterwards you can take her to the four seasons for drinks. or you go downtown and listen to some jazz. or dancing&#151;oh! take her dancing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " you sure are naming a lot of ways to postpone sex, i&#146;ll tell ya&#133;", "answer": " ooh, i miss dating. gettin&#146; all dressed up and going to a fancy restaurant. i&#146;m not gonna be able to do that for so long, and it&#146;s so much fun! i mean not that sitting at home worrying about giving birth to a sixteen pound baby is not fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey, y&#146;know what?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " why don&#146;t i take you out?", "answer": " what?! joey, you don&#146;t want to go on a date with a pregnant lady.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yes i do! and we&#146;re gonna go out, we&#146;re gonna have a good time, and take your mind off of childbirth and c-sections and-and giant baby heads stretching out&#133;", "answer": "  okay! i&#146;ll go with ya! i&#146;ll go! i&#146;ll go with ya.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i&#146;ll be fun.", "answer": " all right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " no. no! yes! ahh. oh, would you look at that monica? i just knocked off all of your top scores, how sad.", "answer": " okay, i&#146;m next.  don&#146;t! don&#146;t start another game! i said i&#146;m next! phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh, i&#146;m sorry. i didn&#146;t hear you over all the winning.", "answer": " chandler! phoebe&#146;s hogging the game!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " who cares? it&#146;s a stupid game.", "answer": " you only think it&#146;s stupid because you suck at it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i don&#146;t suck. it&#146;s sucks. you suck.", "answer": " wait okay, if this game is gonna cause problems between the two of you, then maybe i should just keep it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " no! no-no! i love it! it is a great present! in fact, why don&#146;t you go home and wait for the thank you card?", "answer": " why do you want to play this game so bad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " yeah! it&#146;s not like it spits out a clark bar after every game.", "answer": " okay. phoebe that&#146;s it. come on, get out&#151;out of the chair. get out!  oh come&#133;phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " joey? could you get that?  what are you doing here? i thought you were in your room?", "answer": " no, i&#146;m picking you up for our date. these are for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " ohh, lilies. joey, they&#146;re my favorite. thank you.", "answer": " and, a brownie!  well, half a brownie. actually, it&#146;s just bag. it&#146;s been a long walk from the flower shop and i was startin&#146; to feel faint so&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh man! this is so great! i actually feel like i&#146;m going on a real date! although, i have a hint of morning sickness, and i&#146;m wearing underwear that goes up to about&#133;&#133;there.", "answer": " hey come on now, this is a real date. uh, so&#133;nice place you got here. foosball, huh? pizza box. oh, a subscription to playboy, my kind of woman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " yeah, actually that&#146;s my roommate&#146;s.", "answer": " i would like to meet him. he sounds like a stand up guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " ah yes, but he&#146;s very protective of me so you&#146;d better watch yourself.", "answer": " ah&#133; hey, so this roommate of yours&#133;is he good looking?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " hm-mmm.", "answer": " oh yeah, it must be tough to keep your hands of him, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  yeah, but i&#146;m pretty sure he&#146;s gay.", "answer": " no-no-no-no, he&#146;s not! no! why are you trying to ruin the game? come", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " &#133;which brings us back, of course, to greely&#146;s theory of dominance.  okay, that-that&#146;s all for today. oh, uh does anyone know where the freeman building is?", "answer": " yeah, it&#146;s the new building on avenue a.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what?! that-that&#146;s all the way cross town, i&#146;m supposed to teach a graduate seminar there in ten minutes.", "answer": " ooh, dude. that&#146;s not gonna happen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " now the filet mignon, what comes with that?", "answer": " there&#146;s a side of steamed vegetables.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " emmm. now, instead of the vegetables, is there anyway i can substitute the three-pound lobster?", "answer": " y&#146;know what? bring her both, and i&#146;ll have the same.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " wow! this is shaping up to be a pretty good date&#151;oh, i almost forgot. i didn&#146;t pay you the rent check.", "answer": " oh whoa-whoa-whoa, no roommate stuff. okay? we&#146;re on a date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay. wow! so i get to see what joey tribbiani is like on a date. so do you have any moves?", "answer": " no! no. umm, just myself and if they don&#146;t like me for&#151; i&#146;m sorry i couldn&#146;t even get through that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " i knew it! i knew it. come on tell me your moves.", "answer": " oh alright. umm, well, okay, i usually start by having a bottle of wine sent to my table from a fan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh my god. and that works?!", "answer": " well it does when you combine it with, &quot;this is so embarrassing, i just want to have a normal life!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " oh, you poor little famous man.", "answer": " oh okay, how about this one. i was gonna wait until the end of the night to kiss you, but you&#146;re so beautiful&#133;i don&#146;t think i can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  oh my god! wow! that was fantastic, i almost leaned in. i really almost did!", "answer": " alright, so&#133;so tell me one of your moves.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " alright. so where&#146;d you grow up?", "answer": " that&#146;s your move? boy rach, you&#146;re lucky you&#146;re hot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " come on, just answer the question!", "answer": "  queens.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " and so were-were you close to your parents?", "answer": " yeah, with my mom. yeah, not so much with my dad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. i guess there&#146;s just always been this distance y&#146;know&#151;i mean we both try to pretend it&#146;s not there, but it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  oh.  it&#146;s gotta be rough.", "answer": " yeah, it is. it&#146;s really tough. y&#146;know sometimes i think&#151;wow!! nice move!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " huh?", "answer": " &quot;where&#146;d you grow up,&quot; it&#146;s so simple!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " thank you! and now if you&#146;ll excuse me, i have to go to the rest room.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " and now you&#146;re watching me walk away.", "answer": " yes i am! again so simple!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " you are not going to believe what i did today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " well it clearly wasn&#146;t showering or shaving.", "answer": " i got good. i played this game all day and now i rule at it! they should change the name of it to ms. chandler.  although i-i hope they don&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " wait a minute, you stayed home all day and played ms. pac-man while i went off to work like some kind of chump?!", "answer": " uh-huh, and i got all the top ten scores, i erased phoebe off the board! high five!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " what is the matter with your hand?", "answer": " well i&#146;ve been playing it for like eight hours, it&#146;ll loosen up. come on, check out the scores. oh, and also look at the initials, they&#146;re dirty words.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " chandler, why would you do that?", "answer": " because it&#146;s awesome.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " you think this is clever?", "answer": " well y&#146;know, they only give you three letters, so after a-s-s it is a bit of a challenge.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " hey wait a minute, this one isn&#146;t dirty.", "answer": " it is when you put it together with that one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " ah, well if you don&#146;t clear this off, you won&#146;t be getting one of those from me. but ben&#146;s coming over here tomorrow to play this game, this can&#146;t be there.", "answer": " come on, he won&#146;t even know what they mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " chandler! he&#146;s seven; he&#146;s not stupid.", "answer": " have you talked to him lately?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " all right, look i&#146;m just gonna unplug it.", "answer": " no-no-no, if you unplug it, i&#146;ll have nothing to show for my day! it would be like i was at work.  no!  hey look at that! look at that, it&#146;s still there! this thing must have some kind of primitive rom  chip in it or something!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " honey you-you got to beat your scores!", "answer": " with the claw?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " all right fine. fine, i&#146;ll do it. i&#146;ve just got to get this off the screen. carol and susan are still upset that you taught him pull my finger.", "answer": "  pull my finger&#151;&#151;my hand is messed up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " i am not gonna answer that!", "answer": " oh come on! just pick one! between monica, phoebe, chandler, and ross if you had to, if you had to, who would you punch?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " no one! they are my friends, i wouldn&#146;t punch any of them.", "answer": " chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yeah, but i don&#146;t know why. look at me, i&#146;m having such a wonderful time!", "answer": " me too! hey rach, can i just say i think this is the best date i ever had!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i know!", "answer": " i never laughed so hard&#151;did you see the wine come out of my nose?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " joey, i think everyone saw the wine come out of your nose.", "answer": " i gotta say, i never knew i could enjoy the non-sex part of the date so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " well that is because you have never been on a date with me before.", "answer": " huh. huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " all right, now don&#146;t judge me. i normally wait until my date leaves, but you live here. i&#146;m ripping into this swan.", "answer": " ah! okay, well then you don&#146;t judge me. i&#146;m gonna suck on the cellophane from the brownie i had before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " so tell me, what are joey tribbiani&#146;s end of the night moves?", "answer": " ah, well, if i want the girl to kiss me, first thing i do is make my lips look irresistible.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " how do you do that?", "answer": " now you can&#146;t tell anyone, but uh&#133;i put on shiny lip balm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " yeah, like a moth to a flame, i&#146;m telling ya. okay all right, so now you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " no, i don&#146;t want to tell you.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " because it&#146;s embarrassing.", "answer": " more embarrassing than shiny raspberry lip balm?!  i didn&#146;t say raspberry before did i? all right just-just tell me rach, just tell me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  okay. all right, stand up.  well, when we&#146;re at the door, i lightly press my lips against his, and then move into his body just for a second, and then i make this sound, &quot;hmmm.&quot; okay, i know it doesn&#146;t sound like anything, but i swear it works.", "answer": "  yeah. why&#151;yeah, that would work for ya&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " all right, i gotta go to bed. honey, i had such a wonderful time.", "answer": " oh.  yeah.  me to.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " &#133;you were 50 minutes late to the class, what did you crawl there?!", "answer": " no, i ran. it was really far, and when did people stop understanding the phrase, &quot;get the hell out of my way!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well, why didn&#146;t you just take a cab?", "answer": " ugh, between the traffic that time of day and all the one-way streets it&#146;ll take me twice as long. besides, i teach the class three times a week, who am i? rockefeller?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " well you&#146;re not gonna be able to keep doing this.", "answer": " well i have to. okay? if i don&#146;t, they&#146;ll take the class away from me. and&#133;i already put it in my family newsletter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " you what?", "answer": " you&#146;ve seen it, the geller yeller.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " right. wow!", "answer": " besides, i-i think i figured out a much faster route, i&#146;m sure i can make it this time. i just&#133;i just can&#146;t be afraid to get a little bit&#133;hit by cars.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi! hey, remember how last night we were talking about that movie cujo?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oh yeah, i still can&#146;t believe you haven&#146;t seen cujo. what is wrong with you?", "answer": " relax! it&#146;s not like it&#146;s citizen kane!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " have you ever tried to sit through citizen kane?", "answer": " yeah i know it&#146;s really boring, but it&#146;s like a big deal. anyway, i was thinking about renting cujo sometime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh yeah? all right, let&#146;s do it tonight.", "answer": " well don&#146;t you have that big date tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh right!", "answer": " hey joey, can i ask you something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " after our date last night, did you feel a little weird?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh my god! you did too? it totally freaked me out, what was that?!", "answer": " i don&#146;t know!  i&#146;m-i&#146;m kinda thinking it-it was the lobster&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " oh yeah-yeah, the lobster.", "answer": " yeah, i mean i was up sick all night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah me too, all night.", "answer": " really?! how come we didn&#146;t cross paths?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " okay, i got that. i&#146;ll escape over there. i&#146;ll come back over here. all right, come on ms. pac-man. it&#146;s got&#151;right&#151; well, you&#146;re just a little bitch, aren&#146;t you?", "answer": "  hey, you guys. listen, i&#146;m sorry that i was hogging the game before&#151;&#151;oh my god! your friends have some unfortunate initials!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " they&#146;re all chandler.", "answer": " chandler sucks! he couldn&#146;t have gotten this good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " i did.  but it came at a price.", "answer": " but ben is coming over tonight and he can&#146;t see this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " hey. are you all right? you seem a little distracted.", "answer": " no-no! i&#146;m fine. it&#146;s just&#133; hey, can i ask you something? have you ever looked at someone that you&#146;ve known for a while and then suddenly&#133;suddenly see them a different way?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " you mean like from behind?", "answer": " yeah. yeah, that&#133;that&#146;s exactly it. you&#146;re right. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " ew, y&#146;know what? one time i saw this guy from behind and he seemed like a totally normal guy and then he turned around and it was stephan baldwin!", "answer": "  ooh! yeah. so yeah, so you know exactly what i&#146;m talking about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " totally! wow!  would you excuse me for a sec?", "answer": " oh yeah, sure.  ehhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh my god phoebe, you&#146;re on fire!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " don&#146;t touch me!!", "answer": " don&#146;t touch her!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " all right! go left! go left! go right!! go right!!", "answer": " i can&#146;t!! i can&#146;t!!  noooooooo!!!!!!! you son of a bitch!!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " phoebe!!", "answer": " oh hi ben&#151;no!! don&#146;t look at the machine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " oh god! thank god you&#146;re home! i&#146;m watching cujo.", "answer": "  alone?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " yes! but what is wrong with this dog?!", "answer": " hey, did you get to the part where they&#146;re trapped in the car and cujo&#146;s throwin&#146; himself at the windshield?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " no! no! seriously, what&#146;s wrong with the dog?! wait a minute, what are you doing home so early? what happened to your date?", "answer": " oh uh, it didn&#146;t work out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh. do you want to watch the rest of the movie with me?", "answer": " oh uh, okay. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i never thought i&#146;d say this about a movie, but i really hope this dog dies.  what are you doing over there? come sit here, you protect", "answer": " oh sure, yeah, why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " okay.  okay, that&#146;s him! that&#146;s him! that&#146;s cujo! that&#146;s cujo!", "answer": " all right, i know! i know. yeah, it&#146;ll be okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " oh my god&#133;.what&#146;s he gonna do now? i can&#146;t watch!  oh. seriously, how can you watch this? aren&#146;t you scared?", "answer": " terrified.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}]